<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Ghost Addon on Blog Cine</title>
        <link>https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/tags/ghost-addon/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Ghost Addon on Blog Cine</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:47:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/tags/ghost-addon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>How To Install Ghost Addon Kodi - KodiTricks</title>
        <link>https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/p/how-to-install-ghost-addon-kodi-koditricks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/p/how-to-install-ghost-addon-kodi-koditricks/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/images/Ghost-Addon-Kodi.webp" alt="Featured image of post How To Install Ghost Addon Kodi - KodiTricks" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ghost Kodi Addon is available again as the Shadow Fork in The Crew Repository. The addon is all-in-one and includes sections for TV programming, live television with sports replays, and much more. Ghost is scraping sources online for content, but it also provides playlists that can be accessed in one click and categories. It is recommended to use this addon with &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;http://real-debrid.com/?id=3010885&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;the Real Debrid&lt;/a&gt; to get the most enjoyment. In the guide below, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through step-by-step instructions on installing Ghost Kodi Addon within a few minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;attention-protect-your-privacy-online&#34;&gt;Attention: Protect Your Privacy Online
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be aware that streaming videos may be prohibited in your specific country. Online privacy protection is becoming more essential. We suggest using the use of a VPN. A VPN safeguards your online activity and prevents your service provider and other authorities from scrutinizing your online activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through the use of a VPN, you can also alter your address so that you can gain access to services not available at the place you reside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We suggest using the most reliable Kodi VPN for 2024.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://protonvpn.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;ProtonVPN&lt;/a&gt;: The most efficient way to increase your speed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.privateinternetaccess.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Access VPN for Privacy Access VPN&lt;/a&gt;: The best choice for those with a tight budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://surfshark.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Surfshark VPN&lt;/a&gt;: Great for usability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://nordvpn.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;NordVPN&lt;/a&gt;: Best for average speeds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.cyberghostvpn.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;CyberGhost VPN&lt;/a&gt; is the best VPN for a long trial period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://koditricks.com&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Koditricks.com&lt;/a&gt; is not associated with the creators of Kodi addons. We have no control over the contents of Kodi addons, nor do we recommend that our users take action against copyright violations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ghost-sections-overview&#34;&gt;Ghost: Sections Overview
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Movies&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TV Shows&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Live TV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trakt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Search&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Settings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-ghost-safe&#34;&gt;Is Ghost Safe?
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghost addon is provided through one of the largest and most trusted third-party repositories, THE CREEW REPO. But, since it&amp;rsquo;s not listed in the Kodi repo&amp;rsquo;s official Kodi repo, we cannot be sure of its reliability. Additionally, we don&amp;rsquo;t have the necessary resources to determine whether or not the extension is secure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, I scanned the zip file for THE CREW REPO VirusTotal. The result is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Legally, The situation is the same. It is difficult to tell whether the content available through Ghost is genuine because it pulls content from many sources. This makes it impossible for us to classify Ghosts as legitimate or unlicensed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This leaves you with only one choice: to rely on a VPN to protect your device&amp;rsquo;s data and your information on the internet, such as IP address, location address, and so on. It will be kept secret.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-do-i-set-up-and-install-ghost-kodi-addon&#34;&gt;How do I set up and install Ghost Kodi Addon?
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;install-the-crew-repository&#34;&gt;Install The Crew Repository
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might need to &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/posts/unknown-sources-on-kodi/&#34; &gt;ensure you enable sources from unknown sources&lt;/a&gt; within your Kodi settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter the settings of your Kodi settings and then open the file manager.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose &amp;ldquo;Add source&amp;rdquo; and click on &amp;ldquo;None.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Type in the path &amp;ldquo;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://team-crew.github.io/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://team-crew.github.io/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; and select &amp;ldquo;Done&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on the box to highlight it and then type in an appropriate name, such as &amp;ldquo;the_crew&amp;rdquo; for this media source&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click &amp;ldquo;OK.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Return to your main menu and select &amp;ldquo;Addons&amp;rdquo; on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start the browser for addons by clicking on the small box icon at the top left&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose &amp;ldquo;Install from the ZIP file.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Refuse to ignore the warning message by saying &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open the source &amp;ldquo;the_crew&amp;rdquo; and select the file &amp;ldquo;repository.thecrew-x.x.x.zip&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, wait until a message appears that the repository was installed successfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re unsure how to install the Kodi addon &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://demo.stack.jimmycai.com/posts/set-up-kodi-addons-in-just-three-simple-steps/&#34; &gt;look up our tutorial, including images&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;install-ghost-kodi-addon&#34;&gt;Install Ghost Kodi Addon
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the addon browser, select &amp;ldquo;Install from repository.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose the option to install &amp;ldquo;The Crew Repo.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select your account in the section &amp;ldquo;Video add-ons.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose Ghost (not Ghost TV) and click &amp;ldquo;Install&amp;rdquo; on the bottom right&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check the proper installation for dependencies by clicking &amp;ldquo;OK.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, wait until a message confirms the Kodi addon was installed successfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go back into the main menu, and you will see that the Kodi extension will become available from there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-use-ghost-kodi-addon&#34;&gt;How to Use Ghost Kodi Addon
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not going to leave you to install Ghost! Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick overview of the procedure to make use of the addon:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To begin, click on the Addons tab on the Kodi home screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go to the Video addons tab and start Ghost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you visit the Ghost home screen, you&amp;rsquo;ll find the following seven sections, as depicted in the picture below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s begin by exploring the first part of the Ghost Kodi addon, Movies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are thirteen sub-sections within Movies, such as 1Click, Popular Movies, 3-D Movies, Genre, etc. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to browse movies by genre, go to Genre. Genre section. Movies will be divided into horror, action comedy, and many more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This addon has an additional section for TV shows, also known as television Shows. Ghost Kodi addon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like the Movies category, the On The Air includes sub-folders such as 1Click, On The Air, Genre, Years, Networks, and more. Open the On The Air tab if you&amp;rsquo;d like to view the schedule of popular shows that are currently airing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why would you want the cable box when you can get IPTV using the Ghost Kodi addon? The first step is to go to the Live TV section on the addon&amp;rsquo;s home page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 17 IPTV providers, including Daddy Live, &lt;strong&gt;Fluxus TV&lt;/strong&gt;, Music TV, and many more. In addition, there&amp;rsquo;s an entire new universe of channels and networks within each provider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trakt TV lets you track the latest, find, and share TV shows and films free! And you know what? It&amp;rsquo;s officially compatible with the Ghost Kodi addon. Open Trakt on Ghost&amp;rsquo;s homepage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 17 sub-folders within it, including Movie Lists, TV Lists, TV Calendar series Watchlists, Progress, and so on. If you&amp;rsquo;re unsure about the information you&amp;rsquo;re seeking,, look at the various sub-folders of Trakt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you in search of something particular? For example, a movie or show? Use the Search feature on Ghost to search for anything that comes to your mind fast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simply type in your search term like I entered mine and press OK to launch the search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let Ghost match your search query with its library to create the results list. After a few minutes, you&amp;rsquo;ll get the results of your search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, there are Settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The settings menu in Ghost allows you to tweak the various available options, including General filters, Trakt Debrid, and others. Be careful when altering every Ghost setting if you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with Kodi third-party addons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-integrate-real-debrid-on-ghost-kodi-addon&#34;&gt;How to Integrate Real Debrid on Ghost Kodi Addon
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the Real Debrid integrated, Ghost gets even more efficient. You&amp;rsquo;ll be able to to stream up to 4K quality content with premium links with no buffering, no loss of packets,, and crystal clear quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Premium services such as Real Debrid scrap high-quality links free of charge (but not for anyone) online. The fact is, Real Debrid is paid! Learn more about the pricing and plans at &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;http://www.real-debrid.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;www.real-debrid.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to know the basics of Real Debrid, refer to our article to [what you need to do to use Real Debrid on Kodi or FireStick. When you&amp;rsquo;re all done, follow the steps below to connect Real Debrid and Ghost:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go to the Settings menu in Ghost Kodi. Ghost Kodi addon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on the Debrid tab. Debrid tab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check that Enable debris service is turned on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open Re-auth Real-Debrid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ghost will erase any existing Real Debrid setup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On your smart device, open a web browser, go to &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://real-debrid.com/device&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://www.real-debrid.com/device&lt;/a&gt;, and enter the code when prompted. Follow the on-screen instructions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re not signed in, real Debrid will ask you to input your account information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;7&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once you&amp;rsquo;ve finished, you&amp;rsquo;ll receive an alert via the addon&amp;rsquo;s upper right-hand side of the page, &amp;ldquo;Ghost OK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s all there is to it! Now, you can get high-quality links for your favorite TV and film shows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;last-words&#34;&gt;Last Words
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This guide explains how to install the Ghost Kodi Addon in easy steps. Ghost is a one-stop solution to all your entertainment needs at no cost. From live TV to movie channels, this addon has something for every person.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
